# Joe Binns



#### Junior gameplay programmer excited about innovating.

I'm a physics-oriented gameplay programmer with experience in both Unity (6 years) and Unreal C++ (1 year). Nearing the end of my studies at Futuregames, I'm seeking internships starting **Summer 2024.** 

# **Employment**

#### **Study Support Mentor @ Lund University**

March 2021 — June 2022 · Lund, SE

Provided one-to-one tailored mentoring for BSc students at the Department of Physics.

#### **Unity Developer Intern @ MLabs**

July 2019 — August 2019 · London, UK

Lead development on a realistic, real-time 3D urban environment simulation, for use by an automated transport planning system.

## **Education**

#### **YH Game Programmer @ Futuregames**

August 2022 — December 2024 · Stockholm, SE Specialised in gameplay programming and technical art.

#### **BSc Theoretical Physics @ Lund University**

August 2019 — June 2022 · Lund, SE

Thesis was written on the topic of Combined Regularisation Techniques for Artificial Neural Networks.

#### Contact

joebinns.com



Joe Binns



i<u>oebinns</u>





<u>+46 73 462 47 49</u>

Sweden & UK

# **Technical Skills**

### **Programming Fluency**

C#, Python, Javascript, C++, Java, LaTeX, HTML and CSS.

#### Libraries

Tensorflow, Three.js, LWJGL, Forge Networking and Mapbox.

#### Tools

Git, Perforce, Unity, Unreal, Blender and Photoshop.

# **Select Project**

Stylised Character Controller

Joe Binns 1